‎-民调差距越来越小了 ‎-别去在意民调结果的起伏
- The polls are tightening. -Don't ride the poller coaster.
‎那样会发疯的 唯一重要的民调…
That way madness lies. The only poll that matters--
‎-在11月5日 ‎-对
-November fifth. -Yep.
‎如果我们领先的话 ‎你还会这么说吗
Would you be saying that if we were leading?
‎等我们领先了再来问我 ‎你的大会发言怎么样了
Ask me when we're leading. How is your convention speech coming?
‎差不多了 还有什么事吗
It's getting there. Anything else?
‎有 我想拿莫斯的年龄做文章
Yes. I wanna make an issue of Moss' age.
‎-不行 这个不能做 ‎-要表明他已经脱离时代了
-Not a chance. Not going there. -That he is out of touch.
‎他只看过去 不看未来 ‎新旧观念的对立
He's looking backward, not forward. Old versus new.
‎我们只能讨论他的观点 ‎不能拿他的年龄说事
His ideas, not that he gets to pay less to go to the movies.
‎那就用你做有活力的事 ‎来暗示对比反差
Implied contrast spots, then, with you doing vigorous things.
‎-比如运动 ‎-我打冰球
-Like, you know, sports. -I play hockey.
‎要选美式运动
American sports.
‎嘿 亲爱的
Hey, honey.
‎你好 我上学要迟到了 ‎去了再吃 回头见
Hi. I'm gonna be late for school. I will snack there. See you later.
‎现在就这样了
It's like that now.
‎等她到了青春期 我该怎么办
What am I in for when she turns into a teenager?
‎你想听“会没事的” 还是实话
You wanna hear, "It'll be fine," or you want the truth?
‎会没事的
It'll be fine.
‎剑桥烘焙
‎你指望找到什么 ‎我们昨天没看到的东西
What do you expect to find that we didn't see yesterday?
‎根本就没有
Which was nothing.
‎我是调查员 我要调查
I'm an investigator. I investigate.
‎对你来说很无聊吗 ‎外面有一辆好车空着呢
Is this boring for you? 'Cause there's a nice empty car outside.
‎调查员中情局的“情”字 ‎指的是情报 可不是调查
Investigator? The "I" in "CIA" stands for "intelligence."
‎-我以前是联邦调查局的 ‎-“以前”
-I used to be FBI. -"Used to"?
‎对 我雷厉风行 不计后果
Yeah, well, I move fast and break things.
‎昨天没有这些 所有这些点
This wasn't here yesterday, all these dots.
‎-那是什么 ‎-什么…都别碰
-What is that? -Don't... touch anything.
第三季   第三集
指定
幸存者
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
翻 译   Lysenko
翻 译   小锤子
‎你的文件
Your files.
‎你好
Hi.
‎我和一些有要事要谈的人约了开会
I have a meeting with people who have important things to get to.
翻 译  Bella
‎我昨晚说了
As I mentioned last night,
‎我们考虑将你列入副总统候选人名单
you're being considered for the vice-presidential spot on the ticket.
‎我就直截了当地说了 ‎虽然受宠若惊 但我喜欢现在的职位
Well, let me cut this short. While honored, I like my current position.
翻 译  玉子酱
‎要和重要的人们打交道的那个职位
The one with the very important people?
‎对 而且我的家乡是德克萨斯 ‎莫斯就是土生土长的德州人
Right. And I'm from Texas, which Moss will carry as a native son,
校 对   Lysenko
‎在地区选票上我起不到任何帮助
so I'd be of no help to the ticket, geographically.
‎地域平衡的观念已经过时了
Geographic balance is a relic concept.
‎是这样 我从未参与过竞选 ‎也不感兴趣
Okay. Look, I've never run for office. I don't have the appetite to.
特 效   小螺号
‎老实说 我不确定自己是否擅长
Frankly, I'm not sure I'd be particularly good at it.
‎但即便我无礼迟到 你还是等着我
And yet you waited, despite my rude tardiness.
‎所以你至少有那么一点兴趣
So you must be at least somewhat intrigued.
‎嘿 关于你的姓氏 ‎你父亲是白人吗
Hey, your surname, did you have an Anglo father?
‎不 我改过名
No, that was changed.
‎你介意改回去吗
Would you mind changing it back?
‎好了 如果你是要利用我的拉美背景
Okay. Well, if this is about exploiting my Latino background,
‎-我肯定不奉陪 ‎-拜托 亚伦
-I'll most certainly pass. -Oh, come on, Aaron.
‎别这么敏感 你是完美人选
Don't be so touchy. You're an excellent fit.
‎你加强了柯克曼对外政策的可信度
You bolster Kirkman's foreign policy bona fides,
‎你经验丰富、受人尊敬 ‎你有意见我也要说 你还是个拉美裔
you're experienced, you're admired and, yeah, sue me, you're Latino.
‎拉美裔、千禧一代和城市黑人
Latinos, millennials, urban blacks,
‎上次竞选时有45%的合法选民 ‎留在家中 抱怨无人可选
they were all a huge chunk of the 45% of eligible voters
‎这些人就占了其中的很大一部分
who stayed home last time, whining about having no real choice.
‎我试图向他们解释 向全美国解释
What I'm trying to explain to them, and to all of America,
‎这位总统 最好还加上你 ‎都是全新的尝试 不错的选择
is that the president, and hopefully you, are a new and amazing choice.
‎让我考虑一下
Let me think about it.
‎那你可要仔细考虑
Try thinking about anything else.
‎先生
Sir?
‎我一直在准备竞选连任的纲领要点
I've been working on platform thoughts for the reelect,
‎但我现在是总统 我需要管理国家
but I am president now and I need to govern.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎我知道国会在我任期剩余的几个月里 ‎不会接受我们提出的事项
I know Congress isn't gonna take up our agenda in the waning months of my term,
‎但我们就没有可以做的事了吗
but isn't there something we can do?
‎您的纲领里有什么内容
What's in your platform?
‎真正的税务改革 符合常识的 ‎移民政策 以及惠及全民的医保
Real tax reform, common sense immigration, health care for all.
‎我从国立卫生研究院的某个人那 ‎拿到一份备忘录
I got a memo from someone at NIH
‎说有一种方法也许可以 ‎降低特定药物的价格
about the potential way to lower pricing on certain drugs.
‎很好 找个人跟进一下
That's good. Let's get someone on that.
‎说到药物问题…林复发了
Uh... On the subject of drugs... Lynn has relapsed.
‎-她回到康复中心了 ‎-我很抱歉
-She's back in rehab. -I am so sorry.
‎嗯
Yeah.
‎-你怎么样 ‎-我没事 谢谢关心
-How are you doing? -I'm all right. Thanks for asking.
‎-你要休息一段时间吗 ‎-不必了
-Do you need to take some time? -Not necessary.
‎我只是不希望这事 ‎会影响政府或竞选活动
I just don't want this to become an issue for the administration or campaign.
‎这是私事
It's a private matter.
‎现在还有什么事是私事吗
Does that even exist anymore?
‎-我们不会让这事产生影响的 ‎-谢谢您 先生
-We won't let it become an issue. -Thank you, sir.
‎好了 我们要做一件非常重要 ‎但也极其愚蠢的事
Okay, we've gotta do something very important and extremely stupid.
‎选择我们的颜色
Pick our color.
‎为选举地图选色
For the electoral map.
‎共和党是红色 ‎民主党是蓝色 我们呢
Republicans are red. Democrats are blue. What are we gonna be?
‎-简单 国旗上的第三种颜色 白色 ‎-我们真的想成为白党吗
-Easy. Third color of the flag, white. -We really wanna be the white party?
‎-那就黑色 ‎-寓意不好 还代表邪恶 不行
-Black, then. -Connoting foreboding and malevolence. No.
‎已经有绿党了 灰色比较矛盾
There's already a Green Party. Gray is ambivalent.
‎-黄色 ‎-代表懦弱 而且是尿的颜色 不行
-Yellow? -The color of cowardice and urine. No.
‎紫色 没有党派选这个颜色
Purple. Already used to symbolize neither party.
‎有何事大驾光临
To what do we owe the honor?
‎报到就职
Reporting for duty.
‎能去我办公室聊聊吗
Can we talk in my office?
‎我觉得有一点误会
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
‎总统向我保证 在任免方面
The president assured me that I would have exclusive prerogative
‎我有绝对特权
over hiring and firing.
‎-如果你想打电话给他… ‎-他不信任我
-Well, if you'd like to call him... -He doesn't trust me.
‎不是这样 ‎是我不信任你 而他信任我
Not the case. I don't trust you, and he trusts me.
‎好吧 那你到底是 ‎以什么身份来这里火焰护卫
Okay, so you're here as what, exactly? Keeper of the flame?
‎我来尽我所能做个帮手
I'm here to help in any way that I can.
‎好吧 你是新任竞选活动发言人
Okay, fine. You're the new campaign spokesperson.
‎第一项任务 通知你的前任 ‎他被降职了 你会喜欢他的办公室的
Your first duty, go demote the old one. You'll like his office.
‎不行走开
- -Nope! Go away!
‎-我无事可做 ‎-所有工作都集中在竞选上了 伙计
-I've got zip to do. -All the action's on the campaign, man.
‎艾米丽跑到那边去 我不怪她
I can't blame Emily for bolting.
‎接下来的三个月 我们唯一要做的事
The next three months, the only thing for us to do
‎就是守住记录 杜绝任何失误
is defend the record and prevent any gaffes.
‎这样你就有时间和你原本 ‎不知道她存在的那位女儿联络感情了
Hmm. It gives you time to connect with this daughter you didn't know you had.
‎你怎么知道的
How the fuck do you know about that?
‎隐私已经是陈年旧事了
Privacy's a last century jam.
‎我不知道自己有没有权利
I don't know that I have the right to call
‎称呼这个由我的DNA制造出的 ‎21岁产物为女儿
this 21-year-old product of my DNA my daughter.
‎-但你会联系她的吧 ‎-我不知道会面对什么
-But you're gonna contact her? -I don't know what I'd be getting into.
‎我猜你很擅长在线深挖别人的行踪
I bet you're great at online stalking.
‎-千万别… ‎-我只想知道最基本的事情 好吗
-Don't even-- -All I want is the basics, okay?
‎高中学业考试的成绩、投票记录 ‎有没有在狂欢聚会上喝醉过
SAT score, voting record, whether she's ever been wasted at a rave.
‎光是听你说这些 我就可能被起诉
I could be indicted for even hearing this.
‎我又不是要国家安全局调她的档案
It's not like I'm asking the NSA to draw up her file.
‎你真得找点事做了
You really need to find something to do.
‎我觉得我刚找到了
I think I just did.
‎天花
Smallpox?
‎墙上标记的是它的病毒结构的形状
That was the shape of its viral structure, marked on that wall.
‎怎么会整个地方 ‎都被漂白得一干二净
How? The whole place was scrubbed with bleach.
‎研究员一定知道
The researcher would've known
‎用任何铜制品刮漂白过的墙
scratching a bleached wall with anything copper,
‎比如1982年以前铸造的分币
like a penny minted before '82,
‎就能展现出标记 供人发现
eventually reveals a mark for someone to find.
‎反应过程比较慢 ‎所以直到今天才出现
The kinetics of the reaction were slow. That's why it didn't show up until today.
‎-我们要去哪 ‎-马里兰的德特里克堡
-Where are we going? -Fort Detrick in Maryland.
‎那里存有稀少的天花疫苗
They keep one of the rare stores of smallpox vaccine.
‎及时拿到 我们就会没事
We get it in time, we'll be fine.
‎你在开玩笑吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
‎-你说你会考虑 ‎-反正也不是份多好的工作
-You'll think about it? -It's not a great job, anyway.
‎对 副总统的价值还不如一桶热唾沫
Oh, right. Vice presidency's not worth a bucket of warm spit.
‎他们澄清过 正确的说法是“小便”
They cleaned that up. It's "piss."
‎加纳其实说的是“一桶热小便”
Garner actually said, "Bucket of warm piss."
‎柯克曼只能再就任一个任期
Kirkman can only serve one more term.
‎下次你就肯定是接班人 ‎无论输赢如何
You'd be heir apparent next time, win or lose.
‎我再说得简单易懂一点
Let me make it simpler for you.
‎你想成为美国第一位拉丁裔总统吗
Do you wanna be the first Latino president of the United States?
‎-老天啊 ‎-我的天 当然了
-Jesus Christ. -Oh, my God. Of course.
‎你不希望人们认为 ‎你当选是因为你是拉丁裔
You don't want people thinking you were chosen because you're Latino.
‎-我知道你觉得这很蠢… ‎-说“蠢”都是客气的
-I know you think that's stupid-- -"Stupid" is the nicest word I'd use.
‎好 进来 你提到对制药感兴趣
Yes, come in. You expressed an interest in pharmaceuticals.
‎对 关于非洲撒哈拉以南地区的 ‎寄生虫疾病
Yes, for parasitic worm disease in sub-Saharan Africa.
‎治疗血吸虫病的吡喹酮 ‎一片要21美分
Praziquantel for schistosomiasis costs 21 cents a pill,
‎但蛔虫用阿苯达唑就可消灭 ‎只需3美分
but helminths can be fought with albendazole, costing three cents.
‎这是你的计划
That's what you wanna do.
‎我的计划是 让你去找这位 ‎国立卫生研究院的女士
What I want is for you to get this woman from the National Institutes of Health in
‎学习关于介入权的事情
and learn about march-in rights.
‎越快越好
Now would be good.
‎怎么样
What's up?
‎柯克曼总统从没提起过 ‎他的小姨子是个跨性别者
President Kirkman has never mentioned
‎他究竟在隐藏什么
his transgender sister-in-law.
‎由“为家公民”付费播出
What exactly is he hiding? Paid for by Citizens For Family.
‎莫斯
Moss?
‎是超级政治行动委员会 ‎由一个曾经为他工作的家伙经营
Super PAC, run by a guy who used to work for him.
‎-您要怎么做 先生 ‎-尊重萨莎的隐私 无视这个视频
-What do you wanna do, sir? -Respect Sasha's privacy and ignore it.
‎-这样行不通的 ‎-这条视频已经在疯传
-That's not gonna be possible. - This has already gone viral.
‎所有主流媒体都会播报 ‎这是一场免费的媒体风暴
All the major networks are gonna cover it. It's a free media firestorm.
‎不仅会遭到社会保守人士的抨击
Not only gonna get whacked by the social conservatives,
‎还会因为故意无视而成为 ‎性少数人群活动家的攻击目标
but the LGBTQ activists are gonna hit you for willful neglect.
‎所以我一方面会被指责有所密谋
So, on one hand, I will be accused of having a secret agenda,
‎另一方面 还会被指责回避话题
and on the other, ducking the subject completely.
‎一切都是因为我不想把我的小姨子
All because I don't wanna drag my sister-in-law
‎卷入这个政治漩涡
through this political maelstrom.
‎-说话要小心 别碰到禁忌 ‎-好了 这个话题到此为止
-I'd avoid the word "drag." -Okay, we're done talking about this.
‎-我需要你去查看竞选活动的情况 ‎-好
-I need you to check in with the campaign. -Yep.
柯克曼
‎-这里是艾米丽罗德 ‎-艾米丽
- Emily?
‎祝贺你
- Ta-da. -Oh. Congratulations?
‎走一步看一步吧 ‎有时间你得给我一些建议
Yeah, we'll see. When we have a second, I'm gonna need some pointers.
‎先说两条基本的 别说谎 别吵架
Here are the two basic ones. Don't lie and don't get into an argument.
‎我猜你打来是为了小姨子那件事 ‎该死的莫斯
Okay, well, I assume you're calling about the sister-in-law spot. Fucking Moss.
‎他是个毫无原则、狂妄自大的老混蛋
He's an unprincipled, ego-drunk choad.
‎是啊 但他和总统曾是朋友
Yeah, well, he and the president were friends.
‎-我从没信任过他 ‎-很好 那你赢了
-I never trusted him. -Okay, great. Then you win.
‎你的自然魅力之一就是天真
Naivete is among your elemental charms.
‎你知道萨莎的事吗
Did you know about Sasha?
‎知道 她和第一夫人以前很亲近
Yeah, she and the First Lady were pretty close.
‎她搬去巴黎时 亚历克斯很难过
It was really hard on Alex when she moved to Paris.
‎但她从未想成为众人的焦点
But, you know, she never wanted to be in the spotlight.
‎遗憾的是 平静已经被打破了
Well, sadly, that's all over now.
‎我现在正要去找总统说这件事
That's what I'm on my way to talk to the president about now.
‎回头聊 好
I'll catch you later. Okay.
‎-你好 ‎-你好 我是国立卫生研究院的凯西
- Hi. -Hi. I'm Kasey from the NIH.
‎我是伊莎贝尔
Isabel.
‎没事的 我没有脑膜炎
It's okay, I don't have meningitis.
‎还不确定是不是狼疮 ‎但那个不传染 所以…
Jury's still out on lupus, but that's not contagious, so...
‎你是来教我介入权的
You're here to educate me on march-in rights.
‎好 药品研究开发有很大一部分
Okay. So, a significant portion of drug research and development
‎其实是靠联邦政府 ‎对大学实验室和基金的拨款赞助
is actually funded by federal grants to university labs and foundations.
‎拜杜法案让制药公司
The Bayh-Dole Act allows pharmaceutical companies
‎获许购买任何 ‎由此产生的可销售的药物专利
to then purchase patents on any marketable medications that result.
‎然后给药物随意定价 通常都很高
And charge whatever they like for them, usually exorbitantly.
‎用他们惯用的借口 ‎研发费用之类的鬼话
With their usual justification of R&D costs. Complete bullshit.
‎是啊 不过在拜杜法案中
Yeah. However, tucked away in Bayh-Dole
‎隐藏着一则条款 允许联邦政府介入
is a provision allowing the federal government to march in
‎对那些未能惠及足够多有需求的患者
and take away patents for drugs developed using federal dollars
‎而又是用联邦政府的资金 ‎进行开发的药物取回专利
that aren't reaching an adequate portion of the patients who need them.
‎因为它们花的钱太他妈多了
Because they cost too fucking much.
‎我们可以这样说脏话吗
Are we allowed to swear like that?
‎联邦调查局的人又不会破门而入
The FBI's not gonna burst through the door.
‎所以你是说 ‎总统握有已立法确认的权力
So you're saying that the president possesses previously legislated authority
‎可以迫使某些药物降价
to force certain drug prices down?
‎对
Yes.
‎太棒了
Fuckin' A.
‎她收到了死亡威胁 死亡威胁
She's received death threats. Death threats!
‎你要是不行动 ‎对她的骚扰就不会停止
That harassment isn't gonna stop until you make it.
‎一则声明根本不够 你要让她到这来
A statement alone is not gonna do it. You have to bring her here.
‎让大家看到她只是一个普通人 ‎好让这个话题缓和下去
Normalize her to neutralize this as a talking point.
‎她不应该经历这些事
She doesn't deserve any of this.
‎好吧 你说得对 我会邀请她
Fine. You're right. I'll invite her.
‎莫斯会一直揪着这件事 ‎直到我们正面反击为止
Moss is gonna keep this up until we bloody his nose.
‎我想要流出 ‎他有老年痴呆症基因的消息
I wanna leak that he's carrying the Alzheimer's gene.
‎哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
‎-这种事我们不能瞎编 ‎-不是瞎编
-We can't make up something like that. -Not making it up.
‎你还记得上周三个竞选阵营都参加了 ‎美国以色列公共事务委员会活动吗
You know the AIPAC event that all three campaigns did last week?
‎我们团队进场布置时 ‎他们正在做莫斯那场活动的清场
Our team came in to set up while they were clearing away after Moss,
‎-我擦了他的汤匙 ‎-我不信
-and I swiped his spoon. - I don't believe this.
‎我拿去测验了DNA 结果不言自明
I had it tested for DNA. I think the result speaks for itself.
‎这是窃取基因
That's gene theft.
‎只在八个州是非法的 ‎弗吉尼亚不在其中
Illegal in only eight states, none of them being Virginia.
‎但在所有50个州都是不道德的 ‎而且完全是在侵犯他的隐私
And unethical in all 50, and a complete violation of his privacy.
‎跟他们对萨莎做的事半斤八两 ‎只不过这件事真的关乎选举
Sort of like what they did to Sasha, only this is actually relevant.
‎拜托
Oh, come on.
‎一个正在竞选 ‎四年任期职位的70岁老男人
A 70-year-old man running for a four-year term,
‎认知衰退的风险比常人高12倍
with a 12 times greater-than-normal risk of cognitive decline.
‎你觉得美国人民真的希望 ‎老年痴呆、头脑混乱的莫斯
You think the American people really want an Alzheimer's-addled Moss
‎在凌晨3点接危机电话
answering the 3:00 a.m. crisis call?
‎这绝对是公平竞争
This is absolutely fair game.
‎接下来还要做什么 ‎闯入他的心脏主治医师的办公室
And what's next? A break-in at his cardiologist's?
‎美国人民有权知道
The American people have the right to know.
‎莫斯有权不被知道 ‎如果他这么选择的话
And Moss has a right not to, if that's his choice.
‎我们肯定没有资格
We are certainly not going to be the people
‎在这么私人的事情上替他做决定
to make such a personal decision for him.
‎我不会希望别人替我做这种决定
I wouldn't want anyone making it for me.
‎我不允许 到此为止 谢谢
I forbid this. That's final. Thank you.
‎哈珀先生 潘妮的学校 ‎打电话来找总统
Mr. Harper, Penny's school's calling for the president.
‎-他有空吗 ‎-什么事
-Can he be interrupted? - What's it about?
‎我可以问一下是什么事吗
May I ask what this is concerning?
‎我是幕僚长哈珀
This is Chief of Staff Harper.
‎我知道了 ‎谢谢你通知我们 我会转告总统的
I see. Thank you for informing us. I'll let the president know.
‎你今天这差事可真不好当
Good day not to be you.
‎大部分日子都是这样 ‎不过今天尤其如此
That's most days, but, uh, yeah.
‎又怎么了
What now?
‎-潘妮的学校来电话了 ‎-她没事吧
-Penny's school called. -Is she all right?
‎没有要紧的事 至少 我不会…
Nothing alarming. At least, I wouldn't...
‎我的话…我是说 这是正常…就是…
Not that I'd... I mean, it's part of... You know...
‎还没那么严重
Not so far.
‎有点尴尬
It's a bit awkward.
‎尴尬的感觉已经非常强烈了
I would say the awkwardness is verging on profound.
‎潘妮来月经了 就是…这样
Penny got her period. So... that.
‎两个中年男子在讨论 ‎其中一个人的女儿的初潮
Hmm. Two middle-aged men talking about one of their daughter's first period.
‎这有什么尴尬的
What could be awkward about that?
‎-我不知道我该… ‎-我觉得你出去就好
-I'm not sure what I-- -I think you just leave.
‎她在长大 亲爱的
She's growing up, honey.
‎她在长大
She's growing up.
‎是的 黛安 我们没事
Yeah, Dianne, we're fine.
‎虽然天花很容易传染 ‎但只要在12天潜伏期内注射疫苗
As transmissible as smallpox is, the vaccine is completely effective
‎就不会有问题
if taken within the 12-day incubation period
‎某人要是善良一点 ‎就会早点告诉我 但他没说
that someone nicer would've told me about sooner, but he didn't.
‎是 她想知道这个人 ‎是怎么拿到天花病毒的
Yeah. She wants to know how this guy got his hands on smallpox.
‎他没有 他是用几条分开的DNA ‎组合而成
He didn't. He ordered separate pieces of DNA and put it together.
‎这本应被严密监控 ‎但实际并没有 所以…
Which is supposed to be closely monitored and isn't. Ergo...
‎你听到了吗
Did you get that?
‎梅斯博士认为研究员将天花病毒 ‎DNA上的传染部分隔离开来
Dr. Mays believes the researcher isolated the contagion section of smallpox DNA,
‎然后通过基因编辑 ‎他将它插入禽流感病毒中
and then via CRISPR, he inserted it into the bird flu virus,
‎这就解释了它传染性突然增强的原因
which accounts for its sudden greater communicability.
‎跟她说我们要去多伦多
Tell her we're going to Toronto.
‎多伦多的一家妇产科诊所暴发疫情
There's been an outbreak at an OB-GYN clinic in Toronto.
‎我们要去…是 黛安
We're gonna head... Yes, Dianne.
‎是 我明白 好 再见
Yeah, I got it. Okay. Goodbye.
‎怎么了
What was that?
‎她就是提醒我 我现在是中情局探员 ‎惯用手段应该是秘密行动
She's just reminding me I'm CIA now, whose stock-in-trade is stealth.
‎所以她希望我做事时
So she would prefer that I go about my business
‎不要引起当地警察的注意
without attracting the attention of the local constabulary.
‎-菲利普 ‎-谢谢赛斯
- Thank you, Seth.
‎为什么总统以前没提过他的小姨子
Why has the president not mentioned his sister-in-law before?
‎不提某事和不提及是不同的
Not mentioning something is not the same thing as not mentioning it.
‎希望这个说法不会太过像禅宗公案
If that's not too Zen koan.
‎-赛斯 ‎-是 丹尼斯
-Seth! - Yes, Dennis.
‎柯克曼总统是否试图隐瞒它
Was President Kirkman trying to conceal it?
‎“它”是个有名有姓的人类 ‎因此是隐私
"It" is a human being with a name, which is private.
‎总统的本意是尊重隐私
The president's intent being to respect said privacy,
‎而不是隐瞒任何事 对
not to try to conceal anything. Yeah.
‎赛斯 对于跨性别人士权益 ‎总统持什么态度
Seth, what's the president's position on transgender rights?
‎总统支持一切人权
The president supports all human rights.
‎赛斯总统对跨性别人士权益的态度
Seth! Is the president's position on transgender rights
‎是受自己的小姨子影响吗
influenced by his sister-in-law?
‎立场的问题才刚刚问过
It was just asked what that position even was.
‎显然一个你无法知晓的立场
Obviously, a position you can't identify
‎不可能因为一个亲戚就神奇地产生了
can't magically be brought into being just because of a family relation.
‎说出口之前我还觉得挺有道理的
That made sense in my head before I said it.
‎佳瑞李
- -Gary Lee.
‎-喂 你好 ‎-萨莎 是我 汤姆
-Oui, all么. - Sasha. It's me, Tom.
‎你好 总统先生
Hello, Mr. President.
‎很抱歉让你经历这些
I am so sorry for everything that you're dealing with.
‎由于事出突然 而且威力巨大
Well, the suddenness along with the almost surreal invasiveness,
‎我确实有点摸不着头脑
it has been a bit disorienting.
‎很可怕
It's appalling.
‎我没想到竞选连任会引发这种事
It didn't occur to me that running for a second term would bring this on.
‎-事情已经发生了 ‎-是
- And so it has. -Right.
‎我现在处境尴尬
Well, now I find myself in the awkward position
‎不得不问问你 愿不愿意来华盛顿
of having to ask you if you'd be willing to come to Washington, DC.
‎在政治问题上帮你
To help you politically?
‎不 是帮我们俩
No, to help us both.
‎有人告诉我 ‎阻止对你私人生活的侵扰的唯一办法
I'm told that the only way to stop this intrusion into your private life
‎就是让我们一同在公开场合露面
is for us to stand together, a public appearance.
‎为了恢复隐私 我得放弃它
I need to relinquish my privacy in order to restore it?
‎恐怕是的 但决定权当然在你
I'm afraid so. Obviously, the choice is yours.
‎我会乘早上第一班飞机过去
I'll catch the first flight out in the morning.
‎好 谢谢你 萨莎 等你来
Okay. Thank you, Sasha. I'll see you soon.
‎晚安 汤姆
Good night, Tom.
‎我就是想告诉你和《邮报》的所有人
So I just wanted to let you and everyone at the Post know
‎现在所有和竞选相关的问题 ‎都要交给我
that all campaign-related questions should now be directed my way.
‎至于用泄露信息来交换有利报道的事
And as for trading leaks for favorable coverage,
‎希望不会发生
heaven forfend.
‎再见 霍华德
Bye, Howard.
‎-怎么已经想我了吗 ‎-是嫉妒
-What's up? You miss me already? -Oh. Envious.
‎但像往常一样 我做了决定
But I decided that, as always,
‎既然我可以加入你 ‎就不必犯蠢去嫉妒
jealousy is stupid, when I could just join you.
‎-我不能从赛斯那把你偷过来 ‎-这话有点种植园奴隶主的口气吧
-I can't poach you from Seth. -That's a little plantationy, no?
‎他是我朋友 而且他一直夸你
Well, he's a friend, and he raves about you.
‎-什么 ‎-什么
- What? What? -What?
‎联邦通讯委员会刚刚规定 ‎我们的大会不是大会 而是集会
The FCC just ruled that our convention is not a convention, it's a rally,
‎因此不能免费播出
and thus not entitled to free air time on the networks.
‎我们需要为四天的报道付费
We would have to pay for four days of coverage,
‎这我们付不起
which we cannot afford to do.
‎猜猜投上决定性一票的委员会会长 ‎最初是谁任命的
Take a wild guess who first appointed the commissioner
‎莫斯
-who cast the swing vote. -Moss.
‎你现在开始明白我们在跟 ‎什么样的混蛋竞争了吗 乐观小姐
Are you starting to understand what kind of a dick we're dealing with, Pollyanna?
‎在一个免费的好地方录制 ‎然后放上网
Stage it someplace cool and free. And put it on the Web.
‎-你是白宫那个数码小子 ‎-我猜算是吧
-You're the White House digital guy. -I guess.
‎非常规手段这个可以
So an unconvention? That could work.
‎你现在开始来这里为她工作 ‎安排一下
You work here now, for her. Set it up.
‎-先生 ‎-亚伦 请进
-Sir. - Aaron, please.
‎我本想早点说 但今天很忙
I intended to get to this earlier, but it's been a day.
‎哪天不忙呀
Well, aren't they all?
‎有人想要这份工作真是神奇 ‎更不用说还要拼命争取
It's a wonder anybody even wants this job, let alone chases after it
‎才能得到它
as hard as I'm learning you have to, to get it.
‎总之 我有事找你说
Anyway, I wanted to talk to you about something.
‎非常重要
Something rather momentous.
‎先生你说
Sir.
‎叙利亚
Syria.
‎什么 先生
Sir?
‎我希望你可以悄悄接触冲突各方
I want you to quietly, secretly reach out to the parties involved in the conflict,
‎目标不仅是终止战争
with an eye not just towards a cessation of hostilities,
‎更需要达成一份现实可行的和平计划
but a realistic, workable peace plan.
‎叙利亚正在迅速成为 ‎能点爆第三次世界大战的潜在火药桶
Syria is quickly becoming a potential tinderbox for World War III,
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎我们必须在为时已晚之前 ‎尽一切可能解决它
and we have to do absolutely everything we can to solve this before it's too late.
‎我愿意一试
It will be an honor to try.
‎-还有别的事吗 ‎-没了 这还不够吗
-Was there anything else? - No. Isn't that enough?
‎-好的 谢谢 总统先生 ‎-走吧
-Right. Thank you, Mr. President. -Come on.
‎-抱歉我迟到了 ‎-他是在向你道歉 我已经习惯了
-Sorry to be late. -That was for you. I'm used to it.
‎没关系 请坐吧 哈珀先生
Quite all right. Please, sit down, Mr. Harper.
‎好 今天辅导的目的是…
Okay, well, the purpose of today's session is to--
‎我们的第二回合
Our second go-around.
‎你想知道我们的关系中是什么因素 ‎导致了我如今的状态
You wanna know what in our relationship might help account for my being here.
‎-这是你今天要讨论的东西吗 ‎-让她…
-Is that what you want to discuss today? -Let her--
‎他是个很棒的伴侣
He's a wonderful partner.
‎他很关心我 无可指责 绝对正确
He's attentive and irreproachable and unimpeachably correct.
‎她这不是在表扬我
She doesn't mean that as a compliment.
‎我注意到你没有说他爱你
I noticed that you didn't say loving.
‎这个词不适用
It's not applicable.
‎-这不公平 ‎-我们的婚姻是场交易
-That's unfair. -Our marriage was transactional.
‎没什么值得为此感到羞耻的
There's no shame in it.
‎没必要假装并非如此
There's just no sense in pretending otherwise.
‎是哪种交易
Transactional in what way?
‎她的意思是 我是个穷苦 ‎食品店老板家的儿子 为了钱娶了她
She means I'm the poor-boy grocer's son who married into her money.
‎钱只是附带的 他娶我是因为我父亲
Money was incidental. He married me for my father.
‎你父亲是位杰出的政客
And your father was a prominent politician?
‎他曾是“参议院之狮”
He was the "Lion of the Senate."
‎这不过是拿着中等大学政治学学位的 ‎年轻野心家
Just the ticket for an ambitious young climber
‎向上爬的工具
with a degree in political science from a mediocre university.
‎之前你说你丈夫无可指责
Earlier, you said that your husband was irreproachable.
‎你知道他从未抽过大麻吗 ‎不管这玩意儿现在叫什么
Do you know he's never smoked pot? Or whatever they call it these days.
‎我花了很久去想这到底是…
It took me the longest time to decide if that was, uh...
‎自律、胆小
discipline, timidity,
‎还是单纯为了避免在传记上
or just the avoidance of a biographical detail
‎留下会影响升迁之路的一笔
that might jeopardize his professional ascent.
‎你得出结论了吗
And did you arrive at any conclusions?
‎-这是暗示的指责 ‎-换句话说 都是我的错
- It was an implied rebuke. -In other words, this is all my fault.
‎不都是
Not all.
‎但也不是毫无错处
But not none.
‎我在那等他提副总统的事
I'm there waiting for him to bring up the VP slot.
‎然后我才想起 ‎“傻子”我跟她说要考虑一下的
And it hit me, "Idiot!" I told her I'd think about it.
‎你考虑了吗
So have you?
‎这是自由世界权力第二大的位置
Well, it is the second most powerful position in the free world.
‎今天早上它还是一桶热小便呢
Oh. This morning it was "a bucket of warm piss."
‎我对它的认知是在变化的
Well, my views on the subject are evolving.
‎是对这个职位 ‎还是对于你是否要参选
On the office, or wanting it?
‎你说这可以让我马上成为 ‎总统位置的合理竞争者
You said it would instantly make me a plausible presidential contender.
‎这是我做梦都没想过的事
It's something I've never dreamt of.
‎一个也许不会有第二次的机会
An opportunity that might never come again.
‎但是呢
But?
‎你和罗琳 据我所知还有总统
You and Lorraine and, for all I know, the president,
‎都想让我成为伟大的拉丁裔的希望
want me to be the Great Latino Hope.
‎你不想要这样
Which you're not okay with.
‎这是我一生都在避免的事
I've been looking to avoid that all my life.
‎-我知道你不同意… ‎-这不是我同意或不同意的事
-And I know you don't agree with that-- -It's not for me to agree or disagree.
‎别说了 好吗告诉我你是怎么想的
Just stop, okay? Just tell me what you think.
‎我觉得你是个成年人 你的身份
I think you're a grown-ass man and that your identity,
‎你和这个身份的关系
and your relationship to it, is something you worked out for yourself
‎是你很久以前就解决好的事
a long time ago and will survive
‎在全国竞选中无论可能遇到 ‎什么样的外部定义 你都能承受
whatever external objectification you might be in for in a national campaign.
‎-“可能” ‎-是一定 但我的观点不变
-Yeah, "might be"? -Will be. My point stands.
‎-好吧 ‎-天啊 这是真的吗
- All right. -Holy shit, is this really happening?
‎罗琳 嘿 抱歉这么晚打扰你 我…
Lorraine. Hey, sorry to bother you so late. I...
‎我猜这是你的语音信箱 这并不是…
I guess it's your voice mail, so this is not really, uh...
‎听着 我只是想确认下…
Look, I just wanted to touch base...
‎不 不是要确认…
Yeah, not touch base so much as...
‎哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
‎是这样 我打给你是想告诉你…该死
Look, I wanted to call you to tell you... Shit.
‎很流畅 真的 换我也会这么说
Smooth. Really, I wouldn't change a word.
‎什么开什么玩笑…她的信箱满了
What? You gotta be shitting... Her mailbox is full.
‎-那就发短信给她 ‎-我不要发短信给她
-Well, text her. -I'm not gonna text her.
‎接受参选副总统怎么能发短信说
You don't accept a VP nod via text message.
‎那就发邮件 随便怎样 把这事做了
E-mail, then. Whatever, baby. Just get it done.
‎你想让我怎么办你让我…
What do you want me to do? Do you want me--
‎罗琳齐默
‎罗琳
Lorraine.
‎好 这是可行的 对吗
Okay, this is doable. Yeah?
‎意外总统的非常规活动
An unconvention for the accidental president.
‎-不仅可行 基本也算得上很酷 ‎-算得上
-It's not just doable, it's almost cool. -Almost.
‎这毕竟还是政治
It's still politics.
‎-嘿 你觉得我幼稚吗 ‎-你说那个乐观小姐的笑话啊
-Hey, do you think I'm naive? -That Pollyanna crack?
‎想想是谁说的
Consider the source.
‎罗琳是专业人士 ‎你还是没回答我的问题
Lorraine is a pro, and that wasn't really an answer.
‎-你有原则 ‎-换句话说 我就是幼稚
-You have principles. -Mmm. So in other words, yes.
‎有原则不代表幼稚
Having principles doesn't make you naive.
‎我可能需要再强硬一些
I probably need to toughen up a little.
‎他以为他可以隐瞒潜藏
He thought he could keep it hidden away, lurking.
‎杰瑞德库尔兹秀
‎然后在毫不疑心的美国民众面前 ‎突然提起
And then spring it on an unsuspecting American public,
‎关于变性的激进观点
a radical, alt-gender, alt-sexuality agenda.
‎这是眼不见为净 ‎不公开的边缘化行为
It's such an out-of-sight-out-of-mind, back-in-the-closet marginalization.
‎假装她不存在 希望这事被遗忘
Pretend she doesn't exist and wish it into oblivion.
‎右翼愤怒 左翼难过
The right gets angry, and the left gets sad.
‎我们要把新闻风向扭转过来
We need to seize the news cycle back.
‎们要做非常规活动 ‎但要把时间提前
We're gonna do this unconvention thing, but move it up.
‎-什么时候 ‎-明晚
- To? -Tomorrow night.
‎不可能
That's impossible.
‎萨莎今天到
Sasha lands today.
‎我们拍个合影 然后把新闻故事 ‎拉回我们正在做的事上
We do a photo op, then we change the story right back to what we're running on.
‎这样可以
That should work.
‎如果可行 还要考虑后勤问题
If it were workable. There are logistics involved.
‎比如呢我们只需要 ‎一些摄像机和网络连接
Like what? All we need are cameras and an Internet connection.
‎我不可能这么快就拉来一群人
I can't pull together a crowd that quickly.
‎不需要 这是关键 ‎我直接和选民对话 当面聊
We don't need one. That's the point. I talk directly to the voter, personally.
‎-那你的演讲呢 ‎-找个人通宵写
-Well, what about your speech? -Pull an all-nighter.
‎新闻刚刚曝出莫斯有老年痴呆症基因
Uh, the story just broke about Moss carrying the Alzheimer's gene.
‎什么
What?
‎-我说得不够清楚吗 ‎-不是我做的
-Did I not make myself perfectly clear? -I didn't do this.
‎你有30秒时间解释 让我相信这点
You got 30 seconds to make me believe that.
‎嘿 我知道你和这位小跟班
Hey, I know that you and, you know, Jiminy Cricket here
‎都认为我为了赢 ‎会不择手段 好吧 确实如此
think that I would do anything to win, and, okay, you're right, I would,
‎但我绝不会无视 ‎我的候选人清晰明了的指示
right up to ignoring explicit, unambiguous instructions from my candidate,
‎我从没干过这种事 以后也不会干
which I have never done and would never do.
‎因为这种事只要做一次 ‎职业生涯就完了
Because you do it once, you can kiss your career goodbye.
‎这不是我干的 ‎让我按着一摞圣经测谎
This wasn't me. Polygraph me on a stack of Bibles,
‎拿枪指着我的狗和我妈的脑袋 ‎我也是这么说
holding a gun to my dog's and my mother's head.
‎也许是实验室的人
Someone at the lab, maybe?
‎晚点再说 但刚才讨论的事一定要做
We'll deal with it later, but we are definitely doing this.
‎我们要把新闻从这些破事上转移开来
We are gonna steal the news cycle back from this shit.
加拿大 多伦多
‎-流感大概是三周前爆发的 ‎-隔离在这个诊所
-The flu hit roughly three weeks ago. -Isolated to this clinic?
‎致死率是多少 穆雷医生
Mortality rate, Dr. Mouray?
‎零 患者的症状很严重 ‎我也得了 很不好受
Zero. People got pretty intense symptoms. I caught it, and it kicked my butt.
‎你的情况真吓人
That's scary, in your condition.
‎是有点 但两周后我就痊愈了
A bit. But two weeks later, I was completely fine.
‎大家都是这样
Everyone was.
‎很抱歉没有更劲爆的情况汇报
I'm sorry there's nothing more dramatic to report.
‎当然不是感到遗憾了 ‎但你们可能白来了一趟
Well, not sorry, obviously. But you may have come up here for nothing.
‎你们找到疫情爆发的首例病患了吗
Have you identified a patient zero for the outbreak?
‎还没有
Not really.
‎那段时间这里有任何异常吗
Anything unusual or different here around that time?
‎没有
No.
‎我们确实雇了个新护士
We did hire this new nurse.
‎-我要和这个人聊一下 ‎-是个男护士 但他辞职了
-I'll need to speak to him or her. -Mmm-hmm. A guy. But he quit.
‎那麻烦给我他的联系方式
Then I'll need his contact information, please.
‎我们拥有明确的法定权威
And we have clear statutory authority
‎在这些问题上 ‎对这些药企采取强制措施
to strong-arm these drug companies on this?
‎我去找白宫顾问办公室问过了 ‎他们证实了
I checked with Counsel's office. They signed off.
‎但我只有一个问题
But my only question is,
‎这条法律已经存在好几十年了
this law has been on the books for decades.
‎-为什么没有一届政府试过 ‎-你知道为什么
-Why has no administration tried this? -You know why.
‎取决于总统是否愿意 ‎在选举年得罪大型制药公司
President's willing to tick off Big Pharma in an election year?
‎-他想要管理好国政 ‎-另外 他也可以用这点帮助竞选
-He wants to govern. -Plus, he can run on this.
‎我们要找到完全符合的案例
We need to find the exact right test case.
‎一种太过昂贵的药物 ‎用于治疗常见但却严重的病症
A medication way too expensive for something common and serious.
‎最好是死过人的那种 ‎说这话我真是要下地狱
Preferably where people have died. I am going to hell.
‎要我说你会进天堂
Heaven, anyone asks me.
‎胰岛素
Insulin.
‎海姆代尔制药公司 ‎在过去十年把价格提高了八倍
Helmdale Pharmaceuticals has raised their price eight-fold in the last decade,
‎致使一些糖尿病人限制自己的用药量 ‎引发致命后果
leading some diabetics to ration their dosage with fatal results.
‎把首席执行官叫来
Get the CEO in here.
‎我会和你的办公室协调好时间
I will coordinate with your office on a time.
‎这是你的项目 你负责接待这个人
This is your project. You bring this guy in.
‎好的 先生
Yes, sir.
‎乌龙茶
Oolong.
‎-你还记得 ‎-当然
- You remembered. -Of course.
‎跟我说说 潘妮好吗
So, tell me, how is Penny?
‎有证据显示 她昨天第一次来月经
Evidently she had her first period yesterday.
‎“有证据显示”
"Evidently"?
‎学校没办法打电话给她妈妈 所以…
The school didn't have her mother to call anymore, so...
‎所以他们打给了爸爸 总统先生
So they called her father, the president.
‎更糟的是 他们打电话来留了言
Worse, they left a message.
‎真糟糕 你跟她聊过了吗
Oh, how awful. Have you spoken to her?
‎还没有 她昨晚在朋友家过夜了
Not yet. She stayed at a friend's house last night.
‎可怜的孩子
Poor thing.
‎我很乐意跟她聊聊 如果你愿意的话
I'd be happy to speak with her, if you like.
‎我不知道 我能…
I don't know. I can...
‎没关系 你是对的 ‎我自己也没经历过
It's okay. You're correct. I didn't actually go through it myself.
‎只是感觉我好像有过
It only felt like I did.
‎但这才是最重要的
But that's the whole point.
‎不过你不觉得 她和我这样的人聊
But don't you think that she'd be more comfortable
‎会比和你聊更舒服一些吗
discussing it with someone who looks like me rather than like you?
‎-也许你是对的 谢谢 ‎-好的
-Maybe you're right. Thank you. -Yeah.
‎在来的飞机上 我做了个决定
I made a decision on the flight here
‎我不要成为一个简单的道具
that I not be employed as simply a prop.
‎-萨莎 我让你来… ‎-不 汤姆 让我说完
-Sasha, when I asked you to come-- -No, Tom, let me finish.
‎现在事情已经这样了
Now that the things are as they are,
‎我没有理由再让自己
there's no reason for me to continue to absent myself
‎从这里消失 ‎我要陪在失去了母亲的女孩身边
from this place, from a young girl who's lost her mother.
‎除非你反对
So, unless you object,
‎拍完合影 在阳台上招过手之后
after we do the photo op and wave from the balcony,
‎我想留下 为了她…
I'd like to remain on, for her...
‎也为了亚历克斯
and for Alex.
‎谢谢 潘妮会高兴的
Thank you. Penny would love that.
‎那你呢
And you?
‎当然了
Of course.
‎你从未问过我任何问题
You know, you never asked me any questions.
‎关于我变性的事情
Like, about my transition.
‎大家都有疑问 你肯定也有
I mean, everyone has questions. You must have had some.
‎我想尊重你的隐私
I wanted to respect your privacy.
‎跟我说说 你个人对我是怎么看的
So, tell me, how do you feel, personally, about me?
‎完全接受你
Completely accepting.
‎理智上是这样 那内心呢
Intellectually, sure. But what about viscerally?
‎内心深处你能完全接受吗
I mean, have you fully accepted it viscerally?
‎请说实话
Be truthful. Please.
‎老实说…
Honestly...
‎我不得不说 在内心深处…
I'd have to say that, viscerally...
‎我还在努力接受
I'm still a work-in-progress.
‎我们都是这样 不是吗
Aren't we all?
‎我不知道为什么有必要这样做
I'm not sure why this is necessary.
‎我在前几个职位上 ‎经历过好几次全面的审查
I've been extensively vetted many times over for my previous positions.
‎这次不一样 是政治审查
This is different, a political vetting.
‎和之前的职位比起来 ‎这次你会被问到更私人的问题
You'll be asked about more personal information than for your previous posts.
‎-我们可以开始了吗 ‎-是的 请便
-Shall we begin? -Yes, by all means.
‎你的单身时期很长
You've had an extensive bachelorhood.
‎有没有因此得过任何性传染病
Has it resulted in any sexually transmitted diseases?
‎好吧 一开始就是这么激情的话题
Okay. Talk about starting off with a bang.
‎-没有 ‎-没得过疱疹
-No. -No herpes?
‎-艾滋 ‎-没有就是没有
-HIV? -No means no.
‎和未成年女孩发生过性关系吗
Have you had sexual relations with underage girls?
‎绝对没有
Absolutely not.
‎-未成年男孩呢 ‎-没有
-Underage boys? -No.
‎-男人 ‎-没有
- Men? -No.
‎和已婚女人是否有过性关系
Have you had sexual relations with married women?
‎理论上说是有的 但她那时在分居
Technically, yes. She was separated at the time.
‎我们需要她的姓名和联系方式
We'll need her name and contact information.
‎-为什么 ‎-为了确认
-Why would that be necessary? -For confirmation.
‎但我已经揭示了当时的情况
But I already explained the circumstances.
‎那为什么拒绝合作
Then why object to obtaining corroboration?
‎因为要参选的人不是她 是我
'Cause she's not the one being considered for office, I am.
‎她的隐私应该受到尊重
She deserves having her privacy respected.
‎任何和你有亲密关系的人 ‎一起醉酒、吸毒、赌博
Anyone you've had intimacies with, gotten drunk, high, gambled
‎或是超速的人 ‎无论是在陆地、海洋还是空中
or broken the speed limit with you on land, sea or air
‎接受这次询问都是合理的
is fair game in this inquiry.
‎隐私都被毁了
Privacy be damned.
‎简短来说 是的
In a word, yes.
‎喂
Hello?
‎你好 我是赛斯怀特 ‎我是你的…你联系过我的
Hi. This is Seth Wright. I'm your... You contacted me?
布朗桥大学 学生会
‎我不确定你是否会回复
I wasn't sure you'd respond.
‎没有 当然了 我很高兴你联系了我
No, no, of course. I'm really glad you reached out.
‎是吗我希望不会让你感到奇怪
Are you? I didn't want it to be weird for you.
‎-不 完全没有 ‎-可能还是会有一点吧
-No, no, no. Not at all. -Well, probably a little.
‎也许吧 但同时 也有点…
Maybe. But also, you know, kind of...
‎我想找个比“酷”更好点的词
I'm trying to find a less lame word for "cool."
‎“酷”也不错 我也这么觉得
"Cool" is fine. I think so, too.
‎你想见面吗
So, uh, do you wanna meet?
‎也许一起…喝一杯可能有点怪 ‎但也不是非法的
Maybe grab a... I guess a drink might be a little weird, but not illegal.
‎-我们一起喝一杯吧 ‎-太好了 明晚怎么样
-Let's have that drink. -Great. How's tomorrow evening?
‎明天可以
Tomorrow's good.
‎很好 我刚说了“很好” ‎至少比“酷”好一些
Great. I just said "great." At least I've moved on from "cool."
‎-好的 那就明天见 ‎-明天见
-Uh... Okay, so tomorrow, then? -Tomorrow.
‎好 我会发短信给你
All right. I'll text you.
‎-再见 ‎-再见
- Bye. -Bye.
‎我能感觉到你在看我
I can feel you watching me.
‎抱歉
Sorry.
‎不 我并不内疚
No, I'm not.
‎这是我职业生涯最重要的演讲
This is the most important speech of my career.
‎到下一次演讲前都是
Until the next one.
‎-散个步去 先生 ‎-好吧
-Take a walk, sir. -Fine.
‎这是真的
- This is true. This is true.
‎我知道这个最糟糕了
I know! It's the worst.
‎不
No. No, no, no, no.
‎其实据你母亲的可靠消息
Actually, I have it on good authority from your mom,
‎-生孩子才是最糟的 ‎-哦 天啊 别告诉我
-childbirth is the worst. -Oh, God. Don't tell me that.
‎但她说的是生里奥 ‎不是你 生你很轻松
But Leo's, not yours. Evidently you were a breeze.
‎她说只要在操场上做个深蹲
She said she could've squatted in a field
‎-你就能自己蹦出来 ‎-真恶心
-and you would've popped right out. -That's disgusting.
‎-不 很美妙的 ‎-太恶心了
- That's so gross.
‎是有点恶心
It's kind of gross. It's kind of gross.
‎怎样
So?
‎你谈到的点都涵盖了
It hits all the points you've talked about.
‎但是呢
But?
‎都是其他候选人说过的东西
They're all things other candidates have said.
‎能不能说点选民没听过的
What can you tell voters that they haven't already heard?
‎你有没有在考虑什么 ‎政治常用话题里没有的东西
What have you been thinking about that wasn't on some memo from the policy shop?
‎我知道要说什么了
I know what it is.
‎嘿 没有那个男护士的踪迹可循 ‎他就这么突然出现了
Hey. There's no trace of this male nurse. He just blew in from nowhere.
‎他用了假名字、假身份和假的推荐信
He's got a fake name, false credentials, bogus references,
‎然后就神秘消失了
and then he just ghosted.
‎很可能就是他传染给所有人的
He could be a candidate for who infected them all.
‎我检查了病毒
I examined the virus.
‎和杀死鸟类的病毒完全不同
Entirely different than what killed the birds,
‎也没有来自天花的传染片段
and no smallpox-derived contagion piece.
‎可能就是一次自然爆发
So it could be a natural outbreak?
‎不 病毒里还是进行了基因编辑
No. There was something CRISPR'd into the virus.
‎只是我识别不出这是什么
I just don't recognize what it is.
‎还有别的事 ‎穆雷医生的办公室来电话了
There's something else. Dr. Mouray's office called.
‎-她流产了 ‎-哦 我的天
-She miscarried. -Oh, my God.
‎还有几个其他得病的孕妇也是
As did several other pregnant patients who also got sick.
‎-严重的流感会导致流产吗 ‎-到一定程度的话可以
-Can a bad flu do that? -Up to a point.
‎但我算过了 ‎这样的影响比通常情况要严重
But I ran the numbers. This is in excess of what you'd expect to find.
‎一次诱发集体流产的事件
An induced miscarriage cluster
‎伪装成可能会自然发生的事情
camouflaged to mimic something that might occur naturally.
‎加拿大的流产事件 ‎和佛罗里达的死鸟有什么联系
What connects miscarriages in Canada to dead birds in Florida?
‎也许没有
Maybe nothing.
‎也许有
Maybe not.
‎先生
Sir.
‎当总统的好处之一
One of the nice things about being president,
‎就是没人会告诉你 ‎你早上看起来很糟
no one tells you you look like shit in the morning.
‎我会保持这个传统的 没睡好
I'm gonna observe that tradition. Trouble sleeping?
‎熬夜准备了今晚的演讲 ‎我也是为这个叫你来
Up late working on the speech for tonight, which is why I asked you here.
‎我想开场先宣布我的竞选伙伴
I would like to begin with an announcement of my running mate,
‎我希望由你来担任
and I would like that to be you.
‎我深感荣幸
I'm deeply honored.
‎在你这么说之前
Well, before you say that,
‎我一定要警告你答应下来的后果
I'd be remiss if I didn't warn you about what you were getting into.
‎你会完全失去隐私
Absolute loss of privacy.
‎从任何角度来说 ‎你的生活将不再属于你自己
In fact, in no way, shape or form would your life be your own.
‎我明白
I understand.
‎不 你不明白 ‎这是我需要向你传达的信息
No, you don't. That's what I'm trying to convey.
‎先生 恕我唐突 有件事我想问问您
Sir, if it's not impertinent, there is something I do have to ask you.
‎说吧
Shoot.
‎我想要知道 ‎你选我不是因为我是拉丁裔
I need to know you're not choosing me because I'm Latino.
‎我尊重这个问题
I respect the question.
‎我也希望你尊重我的回答
And I hope you'll respect my answer.
‎我可以说的最简单的回答 ‎就是我雇了合适的人来做这份工作
The easiest thing for me to say is that I hired the right man for the job,
‎虽然我确实这样认为 ‎我的诚实的回答是 我不知道
and as much as I believe that, the honest answer is, I don't know.
‎我对竞选优势的论调无法免疫
I'm not immune to the arguments of an electoral advantage.
‎但我可以告诉你 亚伦
But I can tell you this, Aaron.
‎如果在竞选期间 ‎任何人对你传承的种族因素的态度
If at any point the campaign were to treat your heritage
‎让你感到不舒服
in a way that made you uncomfortable,
‎来告诉我 我会立刻纠正
come to me, and I would make an immediate course correction.
‎我很感激 先生
I appreciate that, sir.
‎我非常荣幸能够接受这份邀请
And it would be my great privilege to accept.
‎拉什先生 ‎我是伊莎贝尔帕尔多 感谢您能来
Mr. Ralsch. Isabel Pardo. Thank you for coming.
‎请坐
Please.
‎-我们请您来的原因… ‎-我们要等哈珀先生吗
-The reason we invited you to-- -Are we waiting for Mr. Harper?
‎由我负责接待您
You'll just be meeting with me.
‎我们要讨论的是介入权
We are here to discuss march-in rights
‎对象是你们公司奇西亚克斯牌胰岛素
as applies to your Keziax brand of insulin.
‎你一定知道
As undoubtedly you know,
‎拜杜法案允许联邦政府介入…
Bayh-Dole allows for intervention by the federal government--
‎据称允许
Purportedly allows.
‎法令如下
Quoting from the statute,
‎“当需要对未能 ‎被合理满足的健康需求
"When action is necessary to alleviate health needs
‎采取措施时…”
which are not being reasonably satisfied--"
‎我们的律师会参与界定 ‎什么是“合理”
Our attorneys would engage on the interpretation of "reasonably."
‎当拥有专利的产品未能 ‎以下再次引述
And when the patented product is not, again, quoting,
‎“按合理条款提供给公众…”
"available to the public on reasonable terms--"
‎白宫想对我们 ‎做生意的方式指手画脚了
White House wants to dictate how we conduct our business?
‎先生 我不是来宣讲道德责任的
Sir, I'm not here to deliver a lecture on moral responsibility.
‎我理解你要对自己的股东负责
I understand you have an obligation to your shareholders,
‎你的董事会 你的底线
your board, your bottom line.
‎我不会使用咄咄逼人的说服话术
I'm not gonna use charged language
‎或是绝望地为公众利益呼吁
or make hand-wringing appeals to a public good
‎这和美国制药业搭不上边
that's essentially an irrelevance to the American pharmaceutical business.
‎你的话听起来已经很咄咄逼人了
Well, that language sounds charged enough to me.
‎正相反 先生 ‎我没有说“良心泯灭”
On the contrary, sir. I didn't use words like "unconscionable,"
‎“贪得无厌” ‎或是我在家常说的“敲诈勒索”
"avaricious," or the term I use at home, "extortionate."
‎我想我们听够了
I believe we've heard enough.
‎无意冒犯 先生 您还要听听这个
Due respect, sir, you haven't.
‎我们儿子亚历克史密斯 ‎本该27岁了 但他已经离开了我们
Our son Alec Smith, who would be 27, is no longer with us.
‎我最想念的是亚历克的拥抱和微笑
What I miss most about Alec is his hugs and his smiles.
‎他咧嘴笑的样子最傻了
He had the goofiest grin,
‎但那个笑容是多么的纯粹、独特 ‎我很想念
but it was so original and so unique that I miss seeing that grin.
‎我儿子的死亡证明上写的官方死因
The official cause of death on my son's death certificate
‎是糖尿病酮症酸中毒
is diabetic ketoacidosis.
‎非官方的死因 是企业的贪婪
Unofficially, the cause of death is corporate greed.
‎胰岛素在近100年前就发明出来了
Insulin was created almost 100 years ago.
‎这些胰岛素公司免费拿到手
These insulin companies, they got it for free,
‎他们近100年来 ‎靠胰岛素赚到的每一分钱
so every penny that they have made off of insulin in almost 100 years
‎都是盈利
has been profit.
‎一小支胰岛素的成本是6美元
It costs $6 to create a vial of insulin,
‎但他们却卖近400美元一支
but they're selling it for almost $400.
‎这是他生命的价钱
The price of his life.
‎亚历克死于限量使用胰岛素 ‎因为他用不起
Alec died from rationing his insulin because he couldn't afford it.
‎现在我的余生都没有儿子陪伴
Now I have to live the rest of my life without my son.
‎因为那些贪婪的人 ‎我失去了灵魂的一部分
A part of my soul is gone because the greedy people
‎他们觉得可以随意提高救命药的价格
think that it's okay to randomly increase the price of life-saving medications
‎直至它们贵到
to the point where they're unaffordable
‎让靠其维系生命的人无力负担
for the people who need them to stay alive.
‎这不公平 不道德 也不正义
It's unfair, it's unethical and it's unjust,
‎必须停止
and it needs to end.
‎为了不再有母亲 ‎因为你们的救命药太贵
So no other mother has to needlessly lose a child
‎而不必要地失去孩子
due to the unaffordability of your life-sustaining drugs,
‎我们建议你们降到这个价位
we suggest you lower the price to this.
‎不然我们就拿走你们的专利 ‎送给竞争公司
Or we take away your patent and award it to a competitor,
‎然后公开这些解释背后原因的视频
and release videos like these justifying why.
‎-来了 ‎-谢谢
- Here we go. -Thanks.
‎我不确定让你喝啤酒我会是什么心情
I don't know how I feel about you having a beer.
‎-赛斯 ‎-不是“爸爸”太快了
-Seth. -Not "Dad"? -Too soon. -
‎-干杯 ‎-干杯
-Cheers. -Cheers.
‎认识你的女儿 第一天 开始了
Meet your daughter, day one. Here it is.
‎表演时间到 总统先生
It's showtime, Mr. President.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎您准备好了就随时开始 ‎五、四、三、二 直播开始
When you're ready. Five, four, three, two, and we're live.
‎各位美国人民 ‎无论你们今晚在哪里观看
My fellow Americans, wherever you are viewing this tonight,
‎在这个新时代 你们似乎有无限选择
your options in this new era seem limitless.
‎所以我选择用这种 ‎不太传统的方式对你们讲话
So I have chosen to speak to you in this less-than-traditional fashion,
‎用手机、笔记本、卫星或电视来直播
streaming via smartphone, laptop, satellite or onto your television,
‎因为我希望你们明白
because I want you to understand that I am trying
‎我想亲自和你们每个人 ‎我的公民们 说话
to talk to each and every one of you personally, as my fellow citizen.
‎不是对任何特别利益群体或美国公司
Not to any special interest groups or corporate America.
‎首先 我想告诉你们我选择了
To begin, I'd like to tell you that I have chosen
‎国家安全顾问亚伦萧 ‎作为我的副总统人选
National Security Advisor Aaron Shore to be my candidate for vice president.
‎-嗨 ‎-你好
-Hi. - Hello.
‎我非常骄傲能有亚伦当我的竞选伙伴
I am very proud to have Aaron as my running mate.
‎-我错过什么了 ‎-只是宣布副总统的部分 去吧
-What did I miss? -Just the VP announcement. Go.
‎所有这些提案的细节信息及更多内容
Detailed information on all these proposals and more
‎都会立即于此次发言结束后 ‎发布在我们的竞选网站上
will be posted on our campaign website immediately following this address.
‎从个人角度 我想请你们思考一些事
On a personal note, there is something I would like you to reflect on.
‎最近几天 有很多 ‎侵犯个人隐私的恶劣行径
Recent days have seen egregious violations of personal privacy
‎涉及我的小姨子和一位竞争对手
involving my sister-in-law and one of my opponents.
‎这些事件 我认为都和
These incidents are connected to what I believe to be
‎个人隐私观念的普遍弱化有关
a general erosion of the concept of personal privacy.
‎有时我们作为公民 ‎在使用社交媒体时
Sometimes we, as citizens, are all too often complicit
‎常常会模糊公共生活 ‎与私人生活的界限
in the erasing of boundaries between our public and private lives via social media.
‎我们还会发现 自己在不知情 ‎且多数时候也违背我们意愿的情况下
And we may also find ourselves unwitting and often unwilling captors
‎隐私受到侵犯 ‎被算法追踪我们的每一次点击
to algorithms that invasively track our every click.
‎鉴于这样的考虑
In consideration of this,
‎我会要求国会新授权一个内阁办公室
I will ask Congress to authorize a new cabinet office,
‎数码科技部
the Department of Digital Technology,
‎为当今超联通的世界提供有效监管
to bring enlightened oversight to our now hyperconnected world.
‎有了互联网 愤怒和恐惧
Via the Internet, it has become too easy to stir anger and fear
‎太容易波及无辜的人
where none is deserved.
‎我的小姨子就是个很好的例子
My sister-in-law is a perfect example of that.
‎萨莎不是偏执人士或活动家的符号
Sasha isn't a symbol for either the intolerant or the activist.
‎她是个美国公民
She is a fellow American citizen,
‎和我们一样 ‎被赋予了相同的不可剥夺的权利
endowed with the same inalienable rights
‎生存权、自由权和追求幸福的权利
to life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness as all of us.
‎现在 我不会天真地认为 ‎因为我们都是美国人
Now, I am not so naive as to believe that simply because we are all Americans,
‎我们就会在所有问题上观点一致
we will all agree on every issue.
‎但如果历史教会了我们什么
But if history teaches us anything,
‎那就是我们的国家 ‎有能力理解和包容彼此
it is that our country's ability to be understanding and tolerant of each other
‎让我们成为民主和世界
has made us one of the great shining lights
‎最闪耀的光明
for democracy and the world.
‎获得包容和接纳有很多途径
We arrive at tolerance and acceptance by varied paths.
‎有些顺理成章 ‎有些则需要时间和经验
Some come by it as a matter of course, and some through time and experience.
‎我有幸在生命中遇见萨莎
I've been blessed to have Sasha in my life,
‎萨莎让我了解了
someone who introduced me to a life journey
‎对自己的认知来说完全陌生的事物
completely foreign to my understanding.
‎我会在你们面前承认
And I will admit before all of you,
‎我包容和接纳她花了些时间
my tolerance and acceptance of her took time,
‎即便是现在 也更多是理智上 ‎而非本能的接纳
and even now, is more intellectual than instinctive.
‎但我会继续每日努力 ‎让自己成为完整的人
But I will continue to work every day to try and make myself whole.
‎我只想督促所有美国人 ‎审视自己的内心
And I can only urge all Americans to look into their own hearts,
‎我相信他们会找到自己的同情与理解
where I believe they will find their own compassion and understanding.
‎我叫汤姆柯克曼
My name is Tom Kirkman,
‎我是美国总统候选人
and I present myself as a candidate for the presidency of the United States.
‎不属于左翼或右翼的党派
Not as a partisan of the right or the left,
‎是你们中的一员 ‎焦虑的大多数美国人
but as one of you, the frustrated majority of Americans
‎我只想为我们这个时代的问题 ‎找到合理的解决方案
who just want sensible solutions to the issues of our time.
‎在请你们为我投票的同时
In asking for your vote,
‎我也请你们和我一起大胆迈步 ‎远离政治常态
I ask you to take this giant leap with me away from politics as usual
‎宣布自己的独立
and declare your independence.
‎谢谢大家 晚安 上帝保佑你们
Thank you. Good night, and God bless you,
‎上帝保佑美利坚合众国
and God bless these United States of America.
白宫 华盛顿
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎莫斯信息的泄露 ‎不是实验室 也不是我
The Moss leak. It wasn't the lab, and it wasn't me.
‎我小看了你 你可别小看我
I underestimated you. Don't underestimate me.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177
本集中所用到的真人采访画面都由纪录片影人提供
他们的观点没有剧本支持 均为个人观点
视频剪辑标准为内容和时长